dailypetition.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy

## Introduction to the Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. 

  * Definition: The word "Site", is, in this privacy policy, reffering to DailyPetition.com
  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. Or until you choose to delete it, wich you can.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and with the knowledge and consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, register on the site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Cookies

Please read our Cookie Notice.

## How we use collected information

DailyPetition.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve customer service_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _\- To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _\- To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate SSL encrypted data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

## Sharing your personal information

DailyPetition.com does NOT and will NOT share personal information of our users with third parties. Even if we will one day, we will ASK THAT YOU GIVE US YOUR CONSENT FIRST! 

### For European Union Users

  * We do not transfer European Union Users information outside of the European Union.
  * We implemented systems to fully comply with GDPR.
  * DailyPetition.com is buid with privacy in mind from the ground up.

## How we protect your rights under GDPR

Right | How we protect you  
---|---  
The rights in the scope of consent (the right to withdraw consent at any time). | We ask you to give consent before giving us yur personal data. If you do not have an account, we do not store any data about you or it is anonymized. The data you fill out in our contact form is not stored or used for any other means than replying to you. The only time when we ask for any of your data and store it is when you create an account. Then, we only ask for the minimal data we need to identify you as a person: name and email address. If you create an account by Facebook, we will also store your oauth_uid and access_token. Also, we store your IP number in anonymized form (last three digits are set to "0"). We use the email address for transactional, non-marketing, communications only. You can always withdraw this consent by deleting your account and all the data we hold about you.  
Time limit for complying with the rights of data subjects | We will try to answer to any complain in 14 days or less. Usually right away.  
Right to basic information (purposes for with the data is beeing precessed) | We only process your data when you create an account.  
Right of access to the information we have about you. | You can chek if we hold any information about you such as an account on the Recover account page.   
Right of rectification entitled to require a controller to rectify any errors in their personal data. (right of correction) | When you log in to your account, you can modify either your name (under Edit Profile) or your email address (under Change Email). You can also edit any petitions you created from the "Edit petition" button in the petition's page.  
Right to erasure (the "right to be forgotten") | You can always delete your all your data from your account. The button is marked in red and says "Delete My Profile". There, you can delete any petitions you created. Also, and any remove your signature form any petition you signed. This applies for both account holders and non-account holders.  
Notifying third parties regarding rectification, erasure or restriction | We do not share your data with any third parties, but if we ever do, we will notify them if you want to delete your data.  
Right of data portability | You can always download your all your data from your account. The button is marked in red and says "Download My Profile". It will be a .zip archive with a .json with all your database info (profile, petitions you created, signatures), photos from petitions you created in .jpg format and videos you posted in .mp4 format.  
Right to object to processing or for the purposes of direct marketing | We do not send direct marketing emails. If you subscribed to web notifications and wish to unsubscribe you can do so in the Settings Page. You can always object to processing by terminating your account. To do this, delete your all your data from your account. The button is marked in red and says "Delete My Profile".   
The right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority | You can lodge a complaint to your supervisign authority in your respective country.  
Right to not be evaluated on the basis of automated processing  | We do not evaluate our users in such ways.  
The period for which the personal data will be stored. | We will keep your account safe and protect your data integrity, availability, confidentiality and durability until such time that you decide to delete your account.  
  
## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate SSL encrypted data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

## Sharing your personal information

DailyPetition.com does NOT and will NOT share personal information of our users with third parties. Even if we will one day, we will ASK THAT YOU GIVE US YOUR CONSENT FIRST! 

### For European Union Users

  * We do not transfer European Union Users information outside of the European Union.
  * We implemented systems to fully comply with GDPR.
  * DailyPetition.com is buid with privacy in mind from the ground up.

## Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

## Notifications

We send out push notifications with important petitions to users who have subscribed to them. You can unsubscribe below:

## Emails

We DO NOT send promotional or marketing emails of any kind. We might send transactional emails like, but not limited to: confirming your email address when registering for a new account, changing your email address or requesting a new password.

## Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

## Facebook Ads

Some of the ads may be served by Facebook Audience Network. You may opt out of the use of targeting for this ads by visiting: [AD Choices](https://m.facebook.com/ads/ad_choices)

## Changes to this privacy policy

DailyPetition.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
This document was last updated on March 20, 2018
